Contact

ssbolden3@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shy-bolden-msn-rn-bc-878a69140 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Research

RN

Languages

Spanish (Limited Working)

French (Elementary)

Certifications

Security Management (Proficiency)

EPIC Hospital Outpatient Department (Proficiency)

EpicCare Inpatient Orders (Proficiency)

Ambulatory Care Nursing

Radiant

Shy Bolden, MSN, RN-BC

Sr. Radiant Consultant at Nordic Consulting Partners, Inc. Richmond, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse and Epic Analyst for the Radiant application. Demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Data Entry, Data Analysis, Quality Assurance and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional graduated with MSN.

Experience

Nordic Consulting Partners, Inc. Sr. Epic Radiant Consultant September 2019 - Present (10 months)

Favorite Healthcare Staffing Registered Nurse August 2009 - Present (10 years 11 months) San Antonio, Texas

Travel Nurse and Agency Nurse in SICU, CV ICU, CCU, & ER

Hctech Consulting Inc Senior Epic Radiant Consultant February 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 8 months)

MD Anderson Cancer Center

6 years 5 months

Clinical Informatics Specialist (EPIC-certified) November 2014 - February 2018 (3 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas Area

EPIC Validation, Go Live, Implementation, Upgrade, Optimization, &Support experience.

Navigators, Narrators, Status Boards, Flowsheets, Orders, & Smartforms build.

Senior Research Nurse

October 2011 - November 2014 (3 years 2 months)

Houston, Texas

Phase 1-3 Clinical Trials for Metastatic Melanoma & Cancer Prevention departments.

Education

Western Governors University
MSN, Nursing Informatics · (2017 - 2019)

UTHealth School of Biomedical Informatics (2016 - 2017)

Southern University and Agricultural and Mechanical College at Baton Rouge

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2005 - 2007)

Louisiana State University Health Sciences Center Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2005)

Louisiana State University

Pre-Nursing Studies · (2001 - 2003)